<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Tutorials on BaconGameDev's Blog</title><link>https://teambaconn.github.io/tutorial/</link><description>Recent content in Tutorials on BaconGameDev's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.145.0</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 14:07:27 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://teambaconn.github.io/tutorial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bacon Combo Graph</title><link>https://teambaconn.github.io/tutorial/combo-graph/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 14:07:27 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://teambaconn.github.io/tutorial/combo-graph/</guid><description>&lt;figure>
&lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://teambaconn.github.io/portfolio/brawl.jpg" width="100%"/>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Bacon Combo Graph is a lightweight Unreal Engine plugin (UE5.3+) designed to help you build complex, animation-driven combat systems fast. With a custom visual editor, native GAS support, and multiplayer-ready design, it&amp;rsquo;s perfect for devs who want clean workflow and fast iteration — especially for melee or combo-heavy games.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="disclaimers">Disclaimers&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>The plugin only supports &lt;code>Unreal 5.3 and onward&lt;/code>. &lt;em>Lower Unreal versions require manual fixes and functional limitation.&lt;/em>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The plugin provides a demo out of the box but &lt;strong>NOT&lt;/strong> a whole shipped game for you to plug and play seemlessly in your own project. You will have to integrate the plugin with your game systems (tutorial below), but after that, creating new content is fast and intuitive.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>This plugin depends on &lt;code>Gameplay Ability System&lt;/code> (GAS) to support multiplayer and other functionalities. &lt;strong>In the short future, I will have a version for non GAS users to use.&lt;/strong>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Animations are not included — use your own or grab packs from the Marketplace. The animations for the demo are from &amp;ldquo;RamsterZ Free Anims Volume 1&amp;rdquo; pack.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Plugin is under active development. More updates coming! Found a bug or have feedback? Just reach out in the &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/pJHvDCGk">Discord server&lt;/a> — I’ll respond as soon as possible.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="features">Features&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Custom editor tool to design complex combo sequence&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Multiple graph nodes, fully extendable to suit your game logics&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Animation driven system integration to communicate seamlessly between Animation / Montage and Gameplay Abilities&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Hitbox system implemented with multiple pre-made shapes (box, sphere, capsule, ring,&amp;hellip;)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Combo window, complex input like one click attack or charge attack (supported by &lt;strong>Enhanced Input System&lt;/strong>) are included and supported by the graph&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>With the features above suitable for making Soul like, beat em up, hack &amp;amp; slash games.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>